MOHAN SINGH

WEB&GRAPHIC DESIGNER

I am a very passionate Web & Graphic designer specialized in creating beautiful, yet functional websites and digital interfaces. I always wanting to grow, learn and try something new. I have 5 years of industry experience and I have worked with many exceptional companies. I love what I do and I work exceptionally hard with who I work with.

EXPERIENCE

April 2022 - 08 Septemb er 2023

SHINE DESZIGN

WEB DESIGNER

 Design web pages and convert into HTML using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, J-Query etc Knowledge about webflow and wordpress

January 2021 - 2022

DOT TECHNOLOGIES

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Design web pages and convert into HTML using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, J-Query etc
- Design Logos, Banners, Posters, Mock-ups, and social media posts.
- Theme Customizations in Shopify and worked with PHP/.NET developers at frond-end.

March 2017 - December 2020

OREM TECHNOLOGIES

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Design web pages and convert into HTML using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, J-Query etc
- Design Logos, Banners, Posters, Mock-ups, and social media posts.
- Converting Photoshop PSD to Shopify store and creating it from scratch.
- Knowledge about creating theme setting to make the shopify section dynamic

WEBSITE LINKS

- . https://nazarianlaw.ca/
- . https://stephaniesanzo.com/
- . https://qb1nation.com/
- . https://liftit.app/
- . https://roomama.co/sg
- . https://relay.vc/



EDUCATION

2013 - 2015

Diploma (Computer Science Engineering)

2011 - 2013

Intermediate / High Schooling

SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3

| Bootstrap3/4/5 | 99% |
|-------------------|------|
| | 99% |
| Responsive | 000/ |
| Photoshop | 99% |
| | 50% |
| Figma | 50% |
| Adobe-Illustrator | 30% |
| | 40% |
| Shopify | 40% |
| J-Query | 40% |
| , Query | 50% |

CONTACT



7652829133



mohansingh7262@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mannu-thakur-a1b413202